var questionsDB = {
    '1': {
        'question': 'What is cellpadding used for?',
        'rightAnswer': 'Change the distance between cell and content',
        'altAnswer1': 'Change the space between elements',
        'altAnswer2': 'Determine alignment of an element',
        'altAnswer3': 'Justify the content of an element'
    },

    '2': {
        'question': 'If you do not include a DESCRIPTION meta tag, the most search engines will simply list what?',
        'rightAnswer': 'The first few words on the page',
        'altAnswer1': 'Nothing',
        'altAnswer2': 'Random line texts',
        'altAnswer3': 'All text above the fold of your page'
    },

    '3': {
        'question': 'Choose the correct html to left-align the content inside a table cell',
        'rightAnswer': 'td align="left"',
        'altAnswer1': 'td valign="left"',
        'altAnswer2': 'tdleft',
        'altAnswer3': 'td leftalign'
    },

    '4': {
        'question': 'How can you open a link in a new browser window?',
        'rightAnswer': "&#60a href='url' target='_blank'&#62;",
        'altAnswer1': "&#60a href='url' new&#62;",
        'altAnswer2': "&#60a href='url' target='new'&#62;",
        'altAnswer3': "&#60a href='url' '_blank'&#62;"
    },

    '5': {
        'question': 'Colspan=n can be added to only what tag',
        'rightAnswer': "&#60td&#62;",
        'altAnswer1': "&#60th&#62;",
        'altAnswer2': "&#60table&#62;",
        'altAnswer3': "&#60div&#62;"
    },

    '6': {
        'question': 'It is the process of removing errors found in the program',
        'rightAnswer': 'Debugging',
        'altAnswer1': 'Editing',
        'altAnswer2': 'Compiling',
        'altAnswer3': 'Running'
    },

    '7': {
        'question': 'What is Java API',
        'rightAnswer': 'A collection of ready-made software components in Java.',
        'altAnswer1': 'An application to display a Java program output.',
        'altAnswer2': 'It is a Java application used to interface two or more systems.',
        'altAnswer3': 'Java applet interface'
    },

    '8': {
        'question': 'Jennie is considering adding a repetition statement within Java. Jennie is unsure of the number of times each loop needs to execute. Which statement best fits the need identified by Jennie?',
        'rightAnswer': 'While',
        'altAnswer1': 'For',
        'altAnswer2': 'If..else',
        'altAnswer3': 'Switch'
    },

    '9': {
        'question': 'in the following tag &#60section class="test" id="section2"&#62&#60/section&#62, which jqery command should be used to hide this element',
        'rightAnswer': "$('.test').hide()",
        'altAnswer1': "$('#test').hide()",
        'altAnswer2': "$('p').hide()",
        'altAnswer3': "$(&#60'section&#62').hide()"
    },


    '10': {
        'question': 'Which Bootstrap - HTML class provides a responsive fixed width container',
        'rightAnswer': '.container',
        'altAnswer1': '.container-fluid',
        'altAnswer2': '.container-fixed',
        'altAnswer3': '.container-responsive'
    },


}